A Guide to the Records of the Office of Vice-President and the Office of Executive Vice-President, Warren W. Brandt, 1958-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the Office of Vice-President and the Office of Executive Vice-President, Warren W. Brandt, 1958-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 3/4
18 Cubic Feet; 18 boxes
This collection consists primarily of the correspondence of Warren Brandt in his capacity as Vice-President of Academic Affairs (1966-1968). However, it also includes many of his files from his period as Executive Vice-President (1968) as well as material from his term as Vice-President and Dean of the Graduate School (1963-1965). There is material and correspondence concerning budget matters, Center for Research in College Instruction of Science and Math, Corps of Cadets, the Dean of Students, EDUCOM, Engineering Experiment Station, ROTC, Student Government Association, Student Activities Committee, Summer School, and Visiting Scholars Program.
Brandt, Warren
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Biographical Note
Born in Lansing, Michigan, Warren W. Brandt received a bachelor's in chemistry from Michigan State University in 1944. He went on to pursue a Ph.D. in analytical chemistry from the University of Illinois. Brandt came to Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) from Kansas State University in 1963. He served as Vice-President and Dean of the Graduate School from 1963 through 1965 before his promotion to Vice-President of Academic Affairs in 1966. He served in this role until 1968, when he became Executive Vice-President of the university. Brandt left VPI in 1969 to become President of Virginia Commonwealth University in Richmond.
Scope and Content
This collection combines the records from Warren W. Brandt's tenure in the Office of the Vice-President (RG 3/4) and the Office of Executive Vice-President (RG 4/1) and is listed as RG 3/4. The collection primarily contains correspondence concerning university business, including letters to Pres. T. Marshall Hahn, academic deans, faculty, parents, and students. Materials from the Academic Council, University Council, National Science Foundation, and the Visiting Scholar Program are also contained in the collection. There are also letters dealing with the rights of women, including a petition seeking to change the regulations governing female students attending the university. The collection also documents issues of racial equality, such as correspondence concerning the Bi-Racial Committee in Blacksburg, a group charged with evaluating the off-campus housing available to African American students.
Materials on the Virginia Associated Research Center (VARC) comprise correspondence, reports, and Governing Committee minutes. VARC was an off-campus graduate facility sponsored by Virginia Tech, the College of William and Mary, and the University of Virginia, in cooperation with the Langley Research Center of NASA. It specialized in applied aerospace research and other basic research in related areas.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by series in chronological order, and each series is arranged alphabetically. Series I covers materials from 1958-1964, Series II contains materials from 1965-1966, and Series III is composed of materials from 1967-1969.
Index Terms
Persons:
Brandt, Warren
Organizations:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute
Subjects:
Faculty; University Archives; University History
Contents List
- Series I: 1958-1964
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) Bulletins, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Council, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academically Deficient – Agriculture Department, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academically Deficient – Architecture Department, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Academically Deficient – College of Arts and Sciences, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Academically Deficient – Business School, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Academically Deficient – Engineering College, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Academically Deficient – College of Home Economics, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Accreditation, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Bulletins, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Admissions – Farrier, Lacy, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Admissions – Farrier, Lacy, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Association, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Association, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Council on Education, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report Samples, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Society for Engineering Education (A.S.E.E.) Goals Study, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Athletic Affairs Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Behavioral Science Commission, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Biochemistry – R.W. Engel, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Biology Department – Orcutt, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Board of Visitors, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Board of Visitors, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Brown, J. Gordon – Student Discipline, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Burchard, Charles, Dean, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Capital Outlay Planning, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Center for Economic Research, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Center for Economic Research, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chemical Engineering – F.W. Bull, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chemical Engineering – F.W. Bull, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Civil Engineering Department, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Civil Engineering Department, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Civilian Senate, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Classroom use of Buildings, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Classroom use of Buildings, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Classroom use of Buildings, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - College Blue Book Listings 1964 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Commencement, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Community Colleges, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Computer Center, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Computer Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Conference on Student Needs and Concerns, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Co-operative Program Evaluation Committee, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Dean, J.W. – Student Affairs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dean, J.W. – Student Discipline, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dean, J.W. – Student Discipline, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Dean of Student Affairs- Petition, surveys and correspondence regarding the Rules for Women Students, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Dean of Student Affairs- Correspondence regarding Bi-Racial Committee in Blacksburg, VA, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Derring, P.N. – Director of Religious Activities, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Entomology Department, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Engineering Mechanics, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Department of English. (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Fabian, R. Craig, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Fabian, R. Craig, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - 4-H Club, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Geology Department, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Glee Club, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Graduate Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Graduate Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Graduate Committee, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Graduate School – Publications, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Hahn, T.M., Jr., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, Dean, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Health, Education and Welfare-Correspondence concerning International Students, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Higgins, T.J., 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - History and Political Science, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Home Economics, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Horticulture Department, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - IBM, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Industry Engineering, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Johnson, Whitney L., 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Jones, Berwyn E., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Jones, Berwyn E., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Kansas State University, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Leadership Camp, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Legislative Apprenticeship Program, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Library Acquisitions, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Library Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Materials Engineering Science, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Mathematics Department, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Mathematics Department, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Metallurgical Engineering, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference On State Science and Technology, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Miller, Jim, 1958-1961 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Mineral Research Lab, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Mining Engineering Department, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - NASA Fellowship, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - NASA – Major Proposal, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - NASA Proposal, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - NASA Proposal – Pre-Doctoral Research Grants, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - National Defense Education Acts, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - National Defense Education Acts – Fellowship Applications, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - National Education Association, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - National Institute of Health, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - NSF – Academic Year Institutes, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - NSF - Computer Proposal, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - NSF - Graduate Traineeship, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - NSF - High School Programs, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - NSF – Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - NSF – Senior Foreign Scientist, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - NSF – Undergraduate Research Proposal, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - New Products, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Philosophy and Religion, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Physical Education Department, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Physics Department, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Placement and Guidance, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Placement Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Position and Salary Commitments, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Poultry, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Religious Affairs Committee - Changes in On-Campus Religious Activities, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Requisition Form, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Research Park, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Richmond Area University Center, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Roanoke Technical Institute, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Scheduling and Registration Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Schewe, Gen. M.W., 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Schewe, Gen. M.W., 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Solicitations, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Statstics Department, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Statstics Department, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Student Organizations, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Teaching Loads – Summer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Tech Festival Association, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - The Techgram, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Television Bulletins – ETV, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - 3M/Age Award (Thermo-Fax), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Traffic Committee, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Virginia Associated Research Center (VARC), 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - VARC, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - VARC, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - VARC, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - VARC – Correspondence and Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - VARC – Correspondence and Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - VARC – Correspondence and Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Agricultural Economics, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Agricultural Engineering, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Agronomy, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Animal Science, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Biochemistry, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Dairy Science, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Entomology, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Extension Education/Administration, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Forestry and Wildlife, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – 4-H Club, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - V.P.I. Faculty – Plant Pathology, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - V.P.I. Faculty Promotions, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Visiting Scholar Program – Department Scholars, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - VSP – University Scholar, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - VSP – University Scholar, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Exchange – Visitor Program, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Water Resources Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Water Resources Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Water Resources Research Institute, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Water Resources Research Institute, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Wesley Foundation, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Wine Awards, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Worcester, Willis G. Dean, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Worcester, Willis G. Dean, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Worcester, Willis G. Dean, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 201)
- Series II: 1965-1966
  - American Association of University Professors, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Academic Deans, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Aerospace Engineering, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Agency for International Development, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - American Institute of Cooperation, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - American Men of Science, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Athletic Affairs Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Athletic Department. (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Capital Outlay, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Cassell, Stuart K., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Catalog Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Center for Economic Research and Business Services, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Center for Research in College Instruction of Science and Math, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Center for Urban and Regional Studies, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Center for Urban and Regional Studies, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Chemistry Department, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Chemistry Department, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Civil Engineering Department, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Civil Engineering Department, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Commencement, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Community Colleges, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Computing Center, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Computing Center, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Computer Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Cooperative Program, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Corps of Cadets, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Counseling Center, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - County Schools, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Dairy Science Department, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Dean, J.W. – Student Discipline, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Dean of Student Affairs - Letters to the Student Body Senate regarding the prohibition of women in men’s dormitory lounges, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Dean of Women - Numerous letters regarding the regulations of women students, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Education – Dr. Beamer, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Engineering Mechanics, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Engineering Mechanics, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Engineering Experiment Station, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - English Department, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Entomology, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Extension Division, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Ferrum College, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Ford Foundation, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Forestry and Wildlife, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Genetics, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Geology Department, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Governor’s Day, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Geology Department, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Grade Summary, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Graduate Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Graduate School Matters, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Grants and Gifts, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall Jr., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Harbison Award, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Health Sciences Advancement Award Proposal, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Higher Education Study Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - History Department, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Home Economics, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Honors Program Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Horticulture Department, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - IBM, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Immigration - Correspondence and forms regarding immigration regulations for faculty from other nations, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Industrial Engineering, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Institute for Academic Deans – Harvard University, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Institute for Academic Deans – Harvard University, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Institute for Academic Deans – Harvard University, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Institute for Academic Deans – Harvard University, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Institutional Research, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Instructional Programs – Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Johnston, G. Burke, Dean, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - Judicial Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Kansas State University, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Land Grant Colleges, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Leaders in American Science, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Library Acquisitions, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Library Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Malpass, Leslie F., Dean, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Materials Engineering Science, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Mathematics Department, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Mechanical Engineering – Dr. S. T. Hsu, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Metallurgy, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Military Affairs Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Mining Engineering, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 323)
  - Mineral Research Lab, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Mining Engineering Department, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Molecular Structure Laboratory, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Midwestern University Analytical Chemistry Conference (MUACC), 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - NASA, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - National Defense Education Act (NDEA). (Box 9, Folder 330)
  - NDEA Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 331)
  - NDEA Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 332)
  - NDEA Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 333)
  - NDEA, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - NSF, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - NSF – Major Proposal – Newspaper, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 340)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 341)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - NSF – Major Proposal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - News and Publications, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Office of Education, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Operations Research Center, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 346)